Distributor : NEW Entertainment
Production : Red Peter Cinematics
Production Investor : Kim Woo Taek
Investor : Jang Kyung Ik
Planner : Park Jun Kyung Person-in-charge : Kim Soo Yeon
Producer : Lee Dong Hwa
Disinfection in progress . Drive slowly
What 's going on ?
Are you going to bury our hogs again ?
It 's just a routine inspection .
There 's a small leak at the bio site .
You don 't have to worry about it .
You also said that the last time .
If you 're going to bury our hogs again
I 'll be really angry .
Don 't worry . Go and do your business .
Go now .
- I can 't believe them . - Goodbye .
Disinfection in progress . Drive slowly
What nonsense are they talking about ?
I don 't believe a word they say .
Goodness . Goodness .
Goodness .
Oh , my goodness .
I 'm so unlucky today .
TRAIN TO BUSAN
Sir , if we sell it right now , other people 's stocks will become useless .
And we don 't even know the reason yet .
And this might be a set-up .
Yes , I understand .
Excuse me ?
No , I 'm not .
I 'm still an amateur .
Okay .
I 'll be waiting for you at the field .
Okay . Goodbye .
Tell Director Kim to come in .
Reason for death of fishes at Jinyang reservoir is unknown
What should we do ?
Sell all of our stocks right now .
Everything ?
Yeah .
It 's going to become a problem .
But how about the stability of the market ?
And what about the small investors ?
- Director Kim . - Sir ?
Don 't think about the small investors .
Sell all of our stocks now .
Okay .
Wait a minute .
What gift do children like nowadays ?
Never mind .
Let 's not go to the trial .
I don 't care what you do .
I 'm going to raise Su-an .
How can you raise a child ?
Do you even talk with her ?
Su-an wants to come over even if she needs to take the trip alone .
Did you know about this ?
What are you talking about ?
Are you really her dad ?
She can 't go there alone .
Then , you can bring her here .
She wants to come here .
I can 't go tomorrow .
Do you know tomorrow is her birthday ?
I know .
Hi .
Did you eat dinner ?
Yeah .
Where is Su-an ?
She 's sleeping in her room .
I can take the train by myself .
Why not ? You can pick me up at the station .
Mom , I have to go . He 's here .
You don 't have to hang up .
I already hung up .
Did you tell mom you 'll go to Busan ?
Su-an , I 'm so busy nowadays .
I think I can go to Busan next week .
Can you wait until then ?
Ah ...
Here you go .
You must 've thought I forgot your birthday .
Happy birthday .
Go on . Open it .
Why ? Don 't you like it ?
For this year 's Childrens Day ...
What is it ? Tell me if there 's something else you want .
Busan .
I want to go to mom .
Tomorrow ...
I already told you .
We can go when I 'm free next time .
No .
Tomorrow .
You always say " next time " . But those are all lies .
I won 't take your time .
I can go there alone .
Are you busy nowadays ?
As usual .
Will you go to Busan with Su-an tomorrow ?
Yes .
Good decision .
When you go to Busan this time , talk with your wife .
Try to solve the problem well with your wife when you meet her .
It 's not right to break the marriage easily like this .
You guys should think about Su-an .
Mom , don 't mind my business .
I 'm so busy nowadays .
Okay .
I believe that you 'll solve the problem well .
Su-an was disappointed since you didn 't go to her recital .
It 's really important time for Su-an too .
Dark clouds covers the sky
The day has come for our farewell
Again ...
It 's okay .
It 's okay . You 're doing fine .
Su-an , continue .
Hello ?
Hi , mom .
Yeah .
No .
Dad is also going .
Okay .
Goodbye .
See you later .
Okay .
I saw you singing at the recital yesterday .
When ?
You didn 't come to my recital .
Although it doesn 't seem like it , I always keep an eye on what you do .
You stopped singing in the middle , right ?
Am I right ?
Yes .
Why did you stop ?
You should 've sung until the end .
Whatever you do , you must finish what you 've started .
It 's worse than not doing it .
What the ...
What 's going on at this wee hours ?
Su-an , are you okay ? You were shocked , weren 't you ?
That startled me .
I think there 's something wrong over there .
To all departing passengers
kindly board KTX 101 heading to Busan .
Where is car 4 ?
It 's that way .
Thank you .
To all departing passengers
the train to Busan will be leaving soon .
Please board the train ...
- Ah ! - Ah .
- Hye-young . - Sir ?
- Your scarf . - Okay .
Fix it .
Let 's be quiet and sit down .
- Okay . - Have a seat .
It 's Jin-hee .
What ? Wow .
Jin-hee , what are you doing here ?
I 'm your cheerleader starting today .
- Oh . - Really ?
Didn 't you hear ?
That 's awesome .
You wanted to become a cheerleader .
- Do you want to sit here ? - Do your best .
Jin-hee , hello .
- Hello . - Oh .
What are you listening to ?
Can you sit elsewhere ?
You 're not listening to anything .
Hey , you should just say ' thank you '
if I say " I like you " .
You should just accept your fate .
She 's right .
You guys are destined for each other .
Accept her . Accept her !
Jong-gil , try this .
When did she make it ?
Why did you bring it ?
It only takes an hour to go to Daejeon .
- It 's okay . - Eat it .
I don 't want to eat it .
Sir , are you on the train ?
Yes , why ?
I 've been receiving a lot of calls .
There was a strike at Ansan factory .
Is that so ?
Gather some information and prepare a report for me .
I 'll be back before lunch .
Okay .
Let me go .
I 'm sorry ...
I 'm really sorry ...
- Excuse me . - Yes ?
- Good morning . - Good morning .
A weird person is on the train .
Where ?
Someone is in the restroom
but he 's not coming out .
- It 's been a while . - She 's right .
Sir , I 'm sorry .
I 'll check right away .
Okay .
Ma 'am ?
Excuse me .
Excuse me ?
Can I see your ticket ?
If you don 't have a ticket , you need to get off the train at the next station .
They 're all dead ...
- They 're all dead ... - What ?
All ... All ...
What is wrong with him ?
Hey , kid .
If you don 't study hard , you 'll end up like him .
My mom told me that whoever says that isn 't a good person .
I guess your mom didn 't study hard .
Sir , you shouldn 't stay here .
Come out first .
Let 's first move to the back .
Is it an emergency ?
Two people are inside , so it 'll take a long time .
So you should use the another restroom .
Go on .
It 's going to take some time .
Honey , how 's it going ?
Ah , I 'm sorry . Take your time .
Take your time .
Use the another restroom . Go on .
She 's gone .
Yeah , take your time .
Ma 'am .
Ma 'am , are you okay ?
What should I do ?
Sir , there 's a patient in car 11 .
Sir !
- Hello ? - Yeah ?
Sir , it 's more serious than we expected .
A lot of things happened during the night .
I 'm not sure right now but it 's not a normal strike .
They say it 's nationwide .
- Is she breathing ? - Hello ?
Is she breathing ?
Yes , she 's breathing .
She 's having a seizure .
Sir , what should we do ?
Hey , I 'll call you later .
Indiscriminate violence at the strike
Oh , my .
They 're going to get hurt .
That 's not right .
What do you mean by that ? Nowadays , people riot over everything .
In the olden days , they got captured .
Hey , you shouldn 't say that .
Oh , my .
Ma 'am ?
What should I do ?
Sir .
Sir , where are you ?
What should I do ?
Sir ?
Min-ji .
Min-ji ?
What is it ?
What is she doing ?
Hey , what are you doing ?
Who is she ?
Hey , who are you ?
Excuse me .
Run away ! Run away quickly !
Everyone run !
Conductor , we have a situation here .
Sir , there 's a fight in the cabin .
- Who is she ? - What 's wrong with her ?
Run ! Run !
Run fast !
Stand up .
Dad !
Run , run !
Honey ?
Hey , Yoon Sang-hwa !
Why were you so noisy ?
Ah , I 'm sorry ...
Help me !
What are you doing ? Save her .
Sir , sir , what 's wrong ?
Are you crazy ?
Honey .
Hey , Sung-kyung !
Can you run ?
Massive violence The victims are increasing
Run !
We need to run away !
Close the door !
Close the door now !
Close it !
Hey , close the door fast .
Just close it !
Oh my goodness !
Oh ! I know him !
How can I lock this ?
Hey , how can I lock this ?
Tell me .
Are you deaf ?
Just let it go .
What ?
They don 't know how to open it .
They attack us when they see us .
What are they ?
Su-an , are you okay ?
Excuse me .
What ?
Don 't you have something to say to me ?
What are you talking about ?
Are you crazy ?
How can you close the door when you saw us running ?
Are you out of your mind ?
Be careful with your words . You 're not the only one in danger .
There 's always jerks like him .
Come here .
I 'm going to kill you right now .
Honey , stop it .
He did that because everyone is scared .
Damn it ...
To all passengers .
Our train won 't stop at Cheon-an , Asan Station .
So please be seated for your safety .
- Let me go through . - What 's going on right now ?
Can I talk to a cabin crew ?
Speaking . What 's the matter ?
Do you know
what 's going on in the train ?
Why aren 't you stopping at the station ?
No , we are aware of it .
We are in a state of emergency now .
But the order was from the control center .
So listen to our order .
What are you talking about ?
The people are going crazy right now .
So stop the train at the station .
Do you get it ?
Wait a minute .
Excuse me .
Can she sit down ?
- She 's pregnant . - Stop it .
- Okay . - Sit .
I 'm fine , though ...
Mom
Yes , mom ?
Seok-woo , are you okay ?
Yeah , we 're okay .
Where are you ? What 's all the noise ?
What 's happening ?
Everyone 's fighting .
Are you guys okay ?
Mom , are you okay ? Are you hurt ?
Seok-woo . Seok-woo ...
Take care of Su-an .
Mom , are you okay ?
Take care of ... Su-an ...
I love her so much .
But she only looks for her mom .
That bastard ...
Mom ?
Dad .
Dad !
Is grandma okay ?
What 's going on ?
What 's happening ?
Su-an , let 's sit down first .
Open the door !
My fellow citizens
violent riots have erupted in major cities
resulting in many injuries to civilians and the police .
Some cities are paralyzed because of these riots .
And some rioters have tried to stop polices buses
and take them over .
You 're so good .
So the government is declaring
a state of emergency to secure the safety of the citizens .
However , the government is able to control this situation
thanks to our rapid response .
We believe that the situation will end soon .
My fellow citizens
don 't be startled by the baseless rumors
and we advice that you stay in your house for your safety .
Everyone needs to stay calm and trust our government and work together .
And based on our intelligence , your safety isn 't in jeopardy .
Analyst Kim Jae-wook
Mom 's phone is turned off .
Can you move faster ?
Su-an , let 's sit here first .
Don 't worry . I 'll call her later .
Jong-gil , come here and sit down .
You 're old yourself . You should sit down .
Come on .
- Honey , come sit down here . - Okay .
Grandma , sit here .
It 's okay .
No , you can sit here .
Hey , do you want to eat this ?
- Thank you . - Thank you .
She 's so kind .
Move faster .
Your bag is irritating me .
Su-an , you don 't have to give away your seat .
What do you mean ?
Giving in to others .
You should think only about yourself . Got it ?
Answer me .
My grandma also had problems with her knees .
Su-an ...
To all the passengers , we are sorry to tell you that
this train will run only until Daejeon .
The army is waiting at Daejeon Station to suppress the riot .
So everyone should leave the train at Daejeon Station .
I repeat , the train will run until Daejeon .
Where can I go right now ?
Yeosu , Uljin , Busan ?
How about Daejeon ?
Excuse me . Let me use the restroom .
Why not ?
Su-an , wait here .
Hey , kid .
Yes ?
Who is he ? Is he your dad ?
Yes .
- Your real dad ? - Yeah .
Why ? He 's weird .
What 's his job ?
A fund manager .
- A fund manager ? - Yes .
He 's a bloodsucker .
They suck the blood of the people .
Hey , you 're in front of a kid .
It 's okay .
Everybody thinks that way , anyway .
Do you want this ?
This is for Jam-jami .
This is Jam-jami . Want to say hi ?
Her name is Jam-jami ?
No , it 's a fetus name .
It 's like a nickname .
She doesn 't have a name yet because her dad is too lazy .
Touch her .
Can you feel her ?
I made her .
- What the ... - I 'm right , am I not ?
The ants
Lieutenant Min from Daejeon
Hello , sir !
I can 't talk right now . Can I call you later ...
Wait , let me ask you something .
What is it ?
I 'm in the train to Daejeon .
The train ?
Ah , then , are you on KTX 101 ?
I guess you know about it .
Are there soldiers at the station ?
Yes , it 's true .
Really ?
Well , I guess it 's safe there .
Ah ... Well ...
Lieutenant Min
will we be safe there ?
Sir , if you come to Daejeon , you 'll be isolated first .
I 'm sorry .
What ?
Hey , I 'm with my daughter .
Can you help the two of us ?
Ah , sir ...
I 'll recommend a good stock for you later .
Then , don 't go out to the main entrance .
Use the east entrance .
I 'll tell my men about you .
Okay . Thank you .
Everyone 's going to die .
What happened here ?
Why is this place so quiet ?
Are we in Daejeon ?
There 's no one here .
Why is it so empty ?
What 's happening ?
This is what I talked about . I mentioned it , didn 't I ?
Conductor !
- Are you a conductor ? - Yes .
How many people can fit in the main car ?
What ?
Let 's get ridof the other cars and go to Busan .
- Are you serious ? - Yes .
- No ! - Why ?
We can 't get out of here .
Where 's the army ?
The army ? Well , I was just following orders ...
My name card is in here somewhere .
I 'm a senior executive of Chunrima Bus .
Every road coming into Daejeon is closed .
So my buses can 't come into Daejeon .
What do you mean by that ?
Dae-jeon isn 't letting people in .
I bet they won 't let us in too .
I heard Busan is still open .
Let 's go there now .
No , no , no . Wait , if that 's true
we need to take everyone with us .
Who are you talking about ?
Let 's check the station first .
Hey !
Damn it .
Don 't mind them . Let 's go .
What are you doing ? Follow me .
Where are you going ?
We 'll use this entrance .
Just us ?
Yes . Don 't mind them . Let 's go .
Why ?
I 'm going that way too .
You should use the main entrance . Just follow the others .
I heard you talking on the phone .
I heard everything
about pulling you two out .
And the others will be isolated .
Wait , Su-an . Let 's just go ...
I want to tell the others .
Su-an , you don 't have to do that .
I have to tell the others .
Don 't bother about others . Just think of yourself .
You only know about yourself .
That 's why mom left you .
Su-an ...
Over here !
Over here ! Help us !
Su-an , don 't move and wait .
Help us !
What the ... Hold me . Hold me .
Hold me .
Go up !
Hurry up !
Over here !
- Hello ? - Sir .
I 'm at Daejeon .
Did you meet my men ?
- I lost contact with them . - What ?
Hello ?
Save me ...
Su-an !
Hurry up .
Do not enter
Hurry up !
- Hurry ! - Hurry !
Hurry !
Close the door .
Okay !
Hurry !
Hey , hurry up !
Close the door !
- Over here . - Come here .
Come over here .
Over here !
- Over here ! - Over here !
Run fast !
Come over here .
Start the train !
People are still there .
- Hurry up ! - Hurry !
- Hurry ! - Over here .
Grandma .
Grandma , stand up .
No .
- Stand up . - Hey !
Hey !
Go up !
Let me in !
When are we going to leave ?
Aren 't we leaving ?
No , my friends are still there .
Hey !
Those who are on board must survive first .
Am I wrong ?
Sir .
Please start the train .
Hey , run .
Run !
Hey , the train .
Run faster .
Hey , stay in focus !
Hey , move !
To the control center , train 101 couldn 't stop at Daejeon .
Can you look for another station ?
Train 101 , we lost contact with the other stations .
To the control center , can we go to Busan ?
Train 101 , we 'll open the railroad until Busan . Over .
Let me know when you contact with Busan .
101 , out .
To all the passengers , for your safety
we will head directly for Busan without making any stops .
Conductor , can you hear me ?
Yes , I can hear you .
Did you contact Busan ?
No , not yet . The connection is unstable .
Just run the train as fast as you can .
We won 't go into Busan if we 're late . Get it ?
Min Young-guk , where are you ?
Ah , I thought you 're dead .
I 'm sorry .
Everyone died except for me .
The number you have dialled ...
- Honey . - Uncle !
Why are you answering the phone ? Where are you ?
In the train . We 're in the train 's restroom .
The restroom ?
What is the number of the car ?
Let me think ...
It 's car 13 !
- Get over here right now . - Sung-kyung .
Damn it .
Did you talk with my kid ? How is she ?
They 're in the bathroom of car 13 .
Are you going to go there ?
Let 's say we made it until there .
Then , how are you going to come back ?
There are people
in car 15 .
Next car : 9
We only have to move three cars only .
I 'll take the lead .
You should be in the middle .
And you should be in the back .
Stop everyone who attack from behind .
By the way , I heard you 're a fund manager .
Well , I guess you know that
I 'll leave you if you become useless .
We 'll move when the tunnel ends .
Let 's go !
Hurry !
Hurry .
Hurry up !
Move out of my way .
Hurry !
Run !
Move !
They stopped when we entered the tunnel .
I guess it 's because of the darkness .
Yes , I think so too .
There are more here .
What should we do ?
We don 't have a choice .
We need to go in .
- Why ? - Give me your cellphone .
Get that out of my face .
Hey , jerk .
How do you feel about meeting your daughter again because of me ?
Tell me .
Are you grateful or what ?
What 's wrong with your ringtone ?
What do you mean ?
How can I change it ?
Am I funny to you ?
You little kid .
How tall are you ?
I 'm 181cm .
Since it 's 10km away
and the train runs with 300km / h ...
What ?
Two minutes .
The upcoming tunnel will give us two minutes .
Can we do it ?
- We don 't have a choice . - We don 't have a choice .
If we miss this tunnel
the next one is 6km away .
I bet you don 't play with your daughter often since you 're busy .
When your daughter gets older
she 'll know why you worked so hard .
A dad always gets blamed and never appreciated .
That 's how life is , isn 't it ?
Why are you looking at me like that ?
Did I sound cool ?
What ?
We saved more people . On our way there .
My friend is coming over here .
What ?
Who 's coming ?
My friend is over there and he 's coming over .
My friend .
He was in car nine and he 'll come here with the rescued people .
The rescued people ?
They have rescued the people .
It 's impossible to not get infected
while passing through the monsters .
Are you sure they 're not infected ?
What are you talking about ?
Look at them .
They don 't know if their family is still alive or not .
And we don 't even know if those people are infected or not but
you want them to come here ?
Really ?
I can 't believe it .
Sir .
Sir , say something .
They 're on their way .
Sir !
Sir ...
Just get over here .
One
two ...
Run !
Hurry up !
Hey , Jin-hee . Jin-hee !
What are you doing ? Open the door !
Jin-hee .
Jin-hee ! Open the door !
Open the door ! Open it !
Open up !
Open the door .
Jin-hee ...
Young-guk
Hey , open the door !
Jin-hee . Jin-hee !
Hey , open the door .
I can 't open the door .
It 's not opening .
Just break it !
Move .
Hurry up !
Those bastards !
Come on !
Sis ...
Young-guk !
Move .
Don 't come here !
Honey , don 't come here .
Go !
You need to go !
Hey !
Take her and go !
- What ? - Just go !
Get out of here .
Please go right now . I 'm losing my strength .
Take care of my wife for me . Okay ?
I 'll stop them here . So , go !
Hurry up !
I 'm sorry ... I 'm sorry .
We need to go now ! We need to go right now !
Yun Seo-young !
Our daughter 's name is Seo-young .
Get it ?
Why did you shut the door ? Why ?
Everyone could 've made it .
Why ?
He 's infected .
He ... He 's infected .
He 's infected !
Look at his eyes .
Look at his eyes !
He 's going to change like those monsters .
Do you want to die ?
We need to kick him out .
Hey !
I think those who came
from the another car can 't stay here .
Please move to another car .
Go away !
- Get out of here . - Go away !
Get out of here .
- Leave . - Leave !
Get out now !
Get out of here !
- Get out ! - Get out !
- Get out ! - Get out right now !
Go away !
- Get out of here ! - Get out right now !
Jin-hee , you 'll be safer here .
No .
It 's scarier here .
I want to go with you .
What ...
Leave !
What are you doing ? Leave !
Okay , let 's go .
Leave ! Get out of here !
Get out of here !
Are you guys deaf ? Get out !
Let 's go .
Leave !
- Tie that side , too . - Faster ! Faster !
Give me some more ties .
I 'm tying it right now . Be quiet .
You should do it !
- Hurry up ! Hurry ! - Give me the pants .
- Hurry ! Hurry ! - Faster !
- Faster ! - Use the pants to tie the door .
We need to tie more ties .
What are you doing ?
You idiot .
Look what happened to you .
Always helping others instead of yourself .
Why did you live like that ?
What was the point ?
Why did you live
like that ...
Hey , shut up .
Be quiet ! Be quiet !
Sit down !
What a load of shit ...
Tie that side , too .
Hey , thank you for everything .
Hey , look at her .
Hey , stop her !
To the control center , we 're on our way to Busan . Confirm the status .
Control ?
Control !
Today is your birthday .
Don 't worry .
I 'll take you to your mom .
Aren 't you scared ?
I 'm scared .
I 'm scared , too .
I was so scared just now
because I thought I can 't see you anymore .
The song I sang yesterday was for you .
That 's why I stopped singing .
Since you weren 't there .
You 'll always be by my side , right ?
Su-an 's mom
The number you have dialled is not available ...
Deputy Kim
Hello , Mr. Kim .
Did you arrive at Busan ?
Not yet .
Where are you ? Is everything okay , there ?
Busan succeeded in keeping the monsters out .
What ? Are you sure ?
Where did you get the information ?
Sir .
This all started from Yu-sun Biotech .
The company we tried our best to save from bankruptcy .
Sir ...
This situation has nothing to do with us , right ?
We just did what we were told .
It isn 't my fault , right ?
Mr. Kim .
It 's not your fault .
Thank you .
Mr. Kim .
To all the passengers , our train will stop at East Daegu Station
since the railroad is blocked .
So we 'll have to wait here for the rescue team ... .
... or move to another train and go to Busan .
After this announcement , I 'll look for a train which is still working
and move it to the left railroad .
- What is he saying ? - The end left railroad .
I hope all the survivors
will move over safely .
I pray for the best .
Will the rescue team come ?
I heard Busan is safe .
We have to go now .
Alright .
Oh , my .
There 's none out there ?
Yes .
Go out first .
We have to find a way to cross over .
Let 's go .
What the ...
Sir !
No ...
What should we do ?
Hey , what should we do ...
Let 's go . We have to go now .
Hold my hand ! Quickly !
Move .
Jin-hee !
What should we do ...
I 'm sorry ...
Dad !
Wake up , dad ! Dad !
Dad ! Dad !
Dad !
What happened ?
Hurry . Hurry up !
Hurry up !
Ah , damn it .
Stand up .
Save me !
Su-an , come here .
Su-an , Su-an !
Uncle !
Su-an !
Su-an , hurry up .
Uncle !
Move ! Move ! Go fast !
Come here !
Come on !
Hurry up !
Dad !
Hey .
I 'm so scared .
Can you take me to my house ?
At home ... At home ...
My mother is waiting for me at home .
The address is
Su-young gu , Busan
Kwonhyun-dong .
Help me ...
Hey .
You 're infected .
No .
That 's not true .
Dad !
No .
Su-an , come here .
Sit here .
Sung-kyung .
Try to listen to me .
I think this is the brake .
If you arrive somewhere safe
just pull this .
You understand ?
Su-an .
Look at me . Look at me , Su-an .
Look at me . Look at me .
Su-an , listen to me .
You need to stay
by her side .
Do you get it ?
And ... you 'll be safe in Busan .
- So ... - Dad , don 't go !
Don 't go ! I 'm sorry !
Dad , don 't go ...
Don 't go ...
Please don 't go ...
Stay with me .
Don 't go ...
Please don 't go .
Dad ! Dad !
Dad !
Dad , don 't go !
Don 't go !
Dad !
Lieutenant Song .
Two subjects are approaching from the tunnel .
A woman and a child , over .
Check if they 're infected , over .
Where did you guys come from ?
Tell him it 's impossible to verify .
We can 't tell if they 're infected or not .
Please tell us your decision . Over .
Kill them , over .
The sky is covered by grey clouds
The day has come to say goodbye
We look forward to the day we meet again
We say our farewell and go our separate ways
Survivors are approaching !
Aloha
Let 's meet again when the flowers bloom
Until we meet again
Gong Yoo
Jung Yu-mi , Ma Dong-seok
Kim Soo-an , Kim Eui-sung
Choi Woo-sik , Ahn So-hee
Director : Yeon Sang-ho